Papers of Diane Wakoski circa 1959-1980 (bulk 1959-1978)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Correspondence, additional records, 1960-1980
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1980-1982 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Martin, John/Black Sparrow Press, 1983-1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Martin, Taffy, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Martin, Valerie, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Martz, Louis L., undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Mary Baldwin College, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Massey, Kent, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts Arts and Humanities Foundation, Inc., undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Matthews, Jack, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Matthews, William (Bill), undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Maurer, John A., undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Maxfield, Jim and Kay, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - McCaffrey, Mark, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - McCord, Howard, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - McGrath, Juliet; Tina; Tom, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - McGraw-Hill/Sounds Seminars, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - McMurry, Jim, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - McPherson, Sandy and Carlile Henry, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Meder, Manfred, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Meiners, Roger and Lynn, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Merians, Linda, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Merill, Jennifer, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Messing, Sera, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Meyer, Tom, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Michigan Poetry Conference, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Michigan State University, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Michigan, University of, Press, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Mieczkowski, Ron, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Carolyn, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Steve, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Miles, Josephine, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Mills, Ralph, undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Mills, Samuel, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Minnesota State Arts Board, undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Minty, Judy, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Minty, Judy: Yellow Dog Journal (Early Version), 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Minty, Judy: Yellow Dog Journal (Final Version), 1978-1979 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Minarik, John, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Missouri Review, undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Modern Literature Conference: East Lansing, Michigan, undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Montgomery, Carol, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Mood, John J.L. and Stephanie, undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Moore, Daniel, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Moore, Gary, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Morgan, Sandy (A. Vance Morgan), undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Morgan, John, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Morris, Carol, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Morrison, Madison, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Morrison, Toni, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Motorcycle Betrayal Poems, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Morrow, Charlie, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Murphy, George, undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Murphy, Mary Frances, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Murray, Michele, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Musher, Andrea, undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - N, undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - National Book Awards (NBA)/National Book Committee, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Nadel, Alan, undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - New American Poetry Circuit, undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - New Directions, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - New School for Social Research, undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - New York Quarterly, undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - New York Time Book Review, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - The New Yorker, undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Newman, Julia, undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Newman, Robert and Dean, Laura, undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Newton, Robert, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Niceswanger, Brund and Mim, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Nims, John F., undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Nin, Anais, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Nisbet, Jeff, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Nonlectures, Suggestions for, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Norris, Kathlene, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Northwest Poetry Circuit, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Notre Dame, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Nottman, Naftali, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Nus, Bob, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - O, undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol, undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - O’Keefe Stephen, undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Oliver, Mary, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Olsen, Tillie, undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Olson, Toby, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - O’Neil, Eugene, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Oppen, George and Mary, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Orr, Greg, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Osing, Gordon, undated (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Osinski, Mike, undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Oury, Scott, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Out Loud Productions, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - P, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Page, William, undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Paintbrush, undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Palmer, Bob, undated (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Paananen, Donna and Vick, undated (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Paris, Bernard J. (Bernie), undated (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Parker, Laura, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Parkinson, Thomas (Tom) and Ariel, undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Parnassus: Poetry in Review, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Pasachoff, Jay M., undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Patch, Jerry, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Pearlson, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Perchik, Simon (Caproni, Perchik and Bayard), undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Perloff, Majorie, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Permissions, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Perry, Connie, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Perry, Ivan, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Peterson, Jim, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Petroski, Catherine, undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Peters, Robert (Bob) and Trachtenberg, Paul, undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Phetteplace, Jim, undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Pinsky, Robert, undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Plantier, Therese, undated (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Platt, Eugene, undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - The Poetry Center, undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - The Poetry Provost, undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - The Poetry Society of America, undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Poets and Writers, undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Poland, undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Pollak, Felix, undated (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - The Pomegranate Press, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Porter, Joe, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Posner, Lou and, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Post, Jon, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Pratt, Annis, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Prelutsky, Jack, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Purser, Candace (Candy), undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Q, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - R, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Radin, Doris, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Randall, Margaret (Meg), undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Raphael, Lev, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Readings- Calendars/ Diaries, 1965, 1967-1968, 1975-1977 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Readings- Before 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Readings- 1968: Preliminary, A-B (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Readings- 1968: C-Ce (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Readings- 1968: Ch-Co (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Readings- 1968: D-H (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Readings- 1968: I-K (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Readings- 1968: L-M (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Readings- 1968: N (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Readings-1968: O-Q (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Readings-1968: R (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Readings-1968: S (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Readings- 1968: T (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Readings- 1968: U-V (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Readings-1968 W (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Readings- 1968 X-Y (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Readings- 1968: “Dead File-Letters Unanswered-6 months or more” A-M (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Readings-1968: “Dead File-Letters Unanswered-6 months or more” N-Y (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Readings- 1969: A-Ci (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Readings- 1969: Cl-H (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Readings- 1969: I-O (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Readings- 1969: P-W (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Readings- 1970: A-Ch (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Readings- 1970: Cl-K (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Readings- 1970: L-R (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Readings- 1970: S-Y (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Readings- 1971: A-Ca (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Readings- 1971: Ce-Q (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Readings- 1971: R-W (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Readings- 1972: A-C (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Readings- 1972: D-M (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Readings- 1972: O-W (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Readings- 1973: A-C (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Readings- 1973: F-Ne (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Readings- 1973: No-W (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Readings- 1974: A-E (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Readings- 1974: F-L (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Readings- 1974: M-Q (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Readings- 1974: R-Y (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Readings- 1975: A-K (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Readings- 1975: L-N (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Readings- 1975: P-W (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Readings- 1976: A-L (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Readings- 1976: M-W (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Readings- 1977: A-K (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Readings- 1977: M-W (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Readings- 1978 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Readings- 1979 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Rechter, Judith, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Recordings, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Reed, Ishmael, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Reed, J.D., undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Rees, Gomer, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Reference Works, undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Relatives, undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Reniker, Sherry, undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Reviews, Notices, Etc: Dancing on the Grave of a Son of a Bitch, undated (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Reviews, etc: Discrepancies and Apparitions, undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Reviews, etc: George Washington, undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Reviews, etc: Greed, undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Reviews, etc: Inside the Blood Factory, undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Reviews, etc: The Megellanic Clouds, undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Reviews, etc: The Man Who Shook Hands, undated (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Reviews, etc: The Moon Has a Complicated Geography, undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Reviews, etc: The Motorcycle Betrayal Poems, circa 1970 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Reviews, etc: Smudging, undated (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Reviews, etc: Trilogy, undated (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Reviews, etc: Virtuoso Literature for Two and Four Hands, undated (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Reviews, etc: Waiting for the King of Spain, undated (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Reviews: General of D.W.; General including D.W.;etc, undated (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Reviews: Readings; Application to buy readings, etc, 1965, 1968-1972 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Reviews: Readings, 1974-1979 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Rhodes, Michelle, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Rich, Adrienne, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Rich, Lynn, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Riordan, Anne, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Robbins, Chris, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Robbins, Tom, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Rochester, University of, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Rockwell, Ruth, undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Roberts, Sheila, undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Rose, George, undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Rosen, Sylvia, undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Rosenberg, David, undated (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Rosenblatt, Joe, undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Rosenthal, Helene, undated (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Rosochacki, Dan, undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Ross, Robert E., undated (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Rossman, Michael, undated (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome, undated (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Route, Debra (Deb), undated (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Rowan, Lewis, undated (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Rubenstein, Carol, undated (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Rudberg, Marilyn, undated (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Ruihles, Glenn R., undated (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Rumaker, Michael, undated (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Russel, Tom, undated (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - S, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - St. James Press, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Salen, Dennis, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Salisbury, Joyce/Ralph, undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Saltman, Benjamin, undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Saltenstall, Katherine (Kathy), undated (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Sanders, Ed, undated (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Sandy, Stephen, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Savitt, Lynne, undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Savitt, Lynne: Lust in 28 Flavors; other poems, undated (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Scanlon, Graciela (Graciela Molas Quiroga), undated (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Shechter, Ruth Lisa, undated (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Schiff, Graenum, undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Schmidt, Eric, undated (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - School of Visual Arts, undated (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Scott, Herb, undated (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Schwerner, Armand, undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Seeman, Julianne, undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Seidman, Hugh, undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Sessions, William, undated (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Sexton, Anne, undated (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Shakely, Lauren, undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Shapiro, Karl, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Sharp, Loretta, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Sheraw, C. Darrel, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Shelton, Lois/ Richard (Dick), undated (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Sherbell, Shepard, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Sherbell, Rhoda, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Sherick, Michael, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Sherman, Susan, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Sherman, Tom, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Shofer, Maria, undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Sholl, Betsy, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Shorb, Terry L., undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Simon, Peggy, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Simon and Schuester, undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Simpson, Louis, undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Sipper, Ralph B., undated (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Sivack, Denis, undated (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Skotkeim, Nadine, undated (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Skrentny, Roger, undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Smallenburg, Harry, undated (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Anna D., undated (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Smith, David J., undated (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Smith, David R. and Annette, 1971-1976 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Smith, David R. And Annette, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Annette, undated (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Smith, Lawrence R. (Larry), undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Leonora Anderson, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Smith, William J., undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Snyder, Gary, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Snow, Karen, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Sparrow, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Spear, Gary, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Speer, Laurel, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Spanel, Anne, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Spencer, Sharon, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Stadler, John and Tippett, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Stadter, John M. Jr., undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Stafford, William, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Stalker, Jackie and Jim, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Stanford, Ann, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Steiner, Herb, undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Stephenson, Bob, undated (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Stodolski, Gerard A.J., undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Stokes, Terry, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - The Stony Brook Poetics Foundation Poetry Press, undated (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Suess, Penelope, undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Sukenick, Lynn and Ron, undated (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Svoboda, Fred, undated (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - The Swallow Press, undated (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Sward, Robert, undated (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Sweeney, Pat, undated (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Syracuse University, undated (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Stolorow, Harriet, undated (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Sumcovski, Zlatko, undated (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Swan, David, undated (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - T, undated (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Tarachow, Michael, undated (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Targ, Roslyn and Bill, undated (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Tarn, Nathaniel, undated (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Taylor, Chuck and Pat, undated (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Taylor, William E., undated (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Terrell, Carroll, undated (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Tharp, Twyla, undated (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Thayler, Carl and Marsha, undated (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Theatre Company of Ann Arbor, Inc., undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Joyce, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Thompson, S. Eugene (Gene), undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Thompson, Tom, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Thorndyke, Nick, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Tillinghast, Richard, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Tipton, James, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Top, Thomas, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Torres, William, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Troyer, Phil, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Turney, Robert, undated, 1969, 1976, January 1977-March 1977 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Turney, Robert, April-May 1977 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Turney, Robert, June-August 1977, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Unicorn Press, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Ursu, Lillianna, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Ussachevsky, Betty and Vladamir, undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - V, undated (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Vas Dias, Robert, undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Vemit, Jimmy, undated (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Venn, George, undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Venn, Steven, undated (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Vermier, Richard, undated (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Vieveck, undated (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Virgilio, Nicholas A., undated (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Vinson, James, undated (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - W, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Wagner, Linda W., undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Wainwright, Carolyn, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Wagstaff, Christopher, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Wakoski, Marie (Mother), undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Wakoski (Father), undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Walcutt, Judy, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Waloman, Anne, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Waldrop, Keith and Rose Marie, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Walsh, Chad, undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Watkins, Evan, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Watterlond, Michael, undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Watterlond, Helen, undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Watts, Richard, undated (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Weaver, Laura, undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Wegela, Fredrick O., undated (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Wiegner, Kathleen, undated (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Wienberger, Andrew B., undated (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Wienberger, Tony, undated (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Wienstein, Norman, undated (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Weller, Sheila, undated (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Welsh, William, undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Wendt, Ingrid, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Whearty, Ray, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Whitney, John (J.D), undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Who’s Who, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Wickes, Molly Westling, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Wilbur, Denise, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Wild, Peter, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Williams, Miller, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Willamson, Alan and Anne, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, Carrington, undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Wilson, J.J., undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Wilson, Keith, undated (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Wilson, Robert, undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Works, undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Wright, Glen, undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Wright, James, undated (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Woyski, Woody, undated (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Wurster, Michael, undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Y, undated (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Yaddo, undated (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Yamrus, John, undated (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Yaple, Henry M., undated (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Yates, David, undated (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Yellin, Herb, undated (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Young, Al, undated (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Young, Geoffrey and Laura, undated (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Young, La Monte and Marian, undated (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Young, William and Co, undated (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Z, undated (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Zawacki, Franklin, undated (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Zinnes, Harriet, undated (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Zukofsky, Lewis, undated (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Zulauf, Sander (Sandy), undated (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Letters By Diane: Anne, Lynn, Tom, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Letters By Diane: Betty, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Letters By Diane: Bev and Jonathan, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Letters By Diane: Bonnie, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Letters By Diane: Bruce, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Letters By Diane: Dave, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Letters By Diane: Darlem, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Letters By Diane: Donna, undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Letters By Diane: Gary, undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Letters By Diane: Gloria, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Letters By Diane: Jeanne, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Letters By Diane: Jeffrey, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Letters By Diane: Jim and Kay, undated (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Letters By Diane: John, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Letters By Diane: Jon, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Letters By Diane: Linda, undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Letters By Diane: Michael, undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Letters By Diane: Mother, undated (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Letters By Diane: Mr. Nice Guy, undated (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Letters By Diane: Pat, undated (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Letters By Diane: Steve and Sylvia, undated (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Letters By Diane: Recipient Unknown, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- Series VII: Published Material, additional records, 1960-1980, undated
  - Subseries 1: Chap Books
    - A, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - B, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - C, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - D, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - E, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - F, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - G, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - H, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - I, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - L, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - M, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - N, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - O, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - P, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - R, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - S, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - T, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - U, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - V, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - W, 1960-1980 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 2: Poems, 1960-1980
    - A-B, undated (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - C,E-G, undated (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - I,L,M, undated (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - N-R, undated (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - S-U, W, undated (Box 69, Folder 25)
- Series VIII: Manuscripts, additional records, 1960-1980, undated
  - Subseries 1: Poems
    - Numbers, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - 5 Artists, 5 Poets, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - A, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - B, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - The Cap of Darkness, circa 1980 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - C-F, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - I-L, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - G-H, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - M, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Motorcycle Betrayal Material, circa 1970 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Motorcycle Betrayal Information and Notes, circa 1970 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - P, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - R, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - S-V, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - W-Z, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2: Other works
    - Reviews/Articles by and about Wakoski, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Essays and other works, A-O, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Discrepancies and Apparitions, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 1)